A Guide to the Records of the Virginia Office of the Secretary of Natural Resources, 1992-2006 (bulk 2002-2005)
Library of Virginia
- Series III. Correspondence and Supporting Documents, Agencies, 1992-2006., Extent: 19 cu. ft. (Box 5-58.)
  - Environmental Quality, Department of, 1992-2006. (Box 24-47.)
    - Waste Management
      - Litter Prevention / Recycling, 2002-2005. (Box 30, Folder 4)
      - Southeast Compact Commission, 2000. (Box 30, Folder 5)
      - Solid Waste Management, 2002. (Box 30, Folder 6)
      - Superfund Sites, 2002. (Box 30, Folder 7)
      - Waste, 2002. (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Water
      - American Electric Power Company, 2002. (Box 30, Folder 9)
      - Army Corps of Engineers, 2002. (Box 30, Folder 10)
      - Army Corps of Engineers, 2002. (Box 30, Folder 11)
      - Army Corps of Engineers, 2002-2003. (Box 30, Folder 12)
      - Army Corps of Engineers, 2003-2004. (Box 30, Folder 13)
      - Army Corps of Engineers, 2004-2005. (Box 30, Folder 14)
      - Broaddus / Hanover County Waste Water Treatment Plant, 1998. (Box 30, Folder 15)
      - Broaddus / Hanover County Waste Water Treatment Plant, 1998-2000. (Box 30, Folder 16)
      - Broaddus / Hanover County Waste Water Treatment Plant, 2000. (Box 30, Folder 17)
      - Broaddus / Hanover County Waste Water Treatment Plant, 2002. (Box 30, Folder 18)
      - Broaddus / Hanover County Waste Water Treatment Plant, 2002. (Box 31, Folder 1)
      - Broaddus / Hanover County Waste Water Treatment Plant, 2002. (Box 31, Folder 2)
      - Broaddus / Hanover County Waste Water Treatment Plant, 2002. (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - Broaddus / Hanover County Waste Water Treatment Plant, 2002-2003. (Box 31, Folder 4)
      - Clean Water Act, 2002. (Box 31, Folder 5)
      - Combined Sewer Overflow Program, 1999-2001. (Box 31, Folder 6)
      - Combined Sewer Overflow Program, 2001-2002. (Box 31, Folder 7)
      - Combined Sewer Overflow Program, 2002-2003. (Box 31, Folder 8)
      - Drought, 2002. (Box 31, Folder 9)
      - Drought, 2002. (Box 31, Folder 10)
      - Drought, 2002. (Box 31, Folder 11)
      - Drought, 2002. (Box 31, Folder 12)
      - Drought, 2002. (Box 31, Folder 13)
      - Drought, 2002-2003. (Box 31, Folder 14)
      - Drought, 2003. (Box 31, Folder 15)
      - Drought, 2003. (Box 31, Folder 16)
      - Elizabeth River Project, 1996-1999. (Box 32, Folder 1)
      - Elizabeth River Project, 2000. (Box 32, Folder 2)
      - Elizabeth River Project, 2001. (Box 32, Folder 3)
      - Elizabeth River Project, 2002. (Box 32, Folder 4)
      - Elizabeth River Project, 2002-2005. (Box 32, Folder 5)
      - Environmental Protection Agency Water Issues, 2002-2005. (Box 32, Folder 6)
      - Fish Consumption Advisory, 2002. (Box 32, Folder 7)
      - Hampton Roads Planning District Commission, 2002. (Box 32, Folder 8)
      - Hampton Roads Planning District Commission, 2003. (Box 32, Folder 9)
      - Hampton Roads Planning District Commission, 2003-2004. (Box 32, Folder 10)
      - Hampton Roads Sanitation District, 2001-2002. (Box 32, Folder 11)
      - Hampton Roads Sanitation District, 2003-2004. (Box 32, Folder 12)
      - Holtzman Travel Center (Mauzy, Va.), 2002. (Box 32, Folder 13)
      - Holtzman Travel Center (Mauzy, Va.), 2002. (Box 32, Folder 14)
      - James River Basin Study, 1992. (Box 32, Folder 15)
      - James River Basin Study, 1992. (Box 33, Folder 1)
      - James River Basin Study, 1992. (Box 33, Folder 2)
      - James River Basin Study, 1992. (Box 33, Folder 3)
      - James River Basin Study, 1992. (Box 33, Folder 4)
      - James River Basin Study, 2001-2002. (Box 33, Folder 5)
      - James River Basin Study, 2002. (Box 33, Folder 6)
      - James River Basin Study, 2002-2003. (Box 33, Folder 7)
      - Joint Meeting of the SWCB, CBLAB and VSWCD, 2005. (Box 33, Folder 8)
      - King William Reservoir Project, 1994. (Box 33, Folder 9)
      - King William Reservoir Project, 1994. (Box 33, Folder 10)
      - King William Reservoir Project, 1996. (Box 33, Folder 11)
      - King William Reservoir Project, 1996-1997. (Box 33, Folder 12)
      - King William Reservoir Project, 1997. (Box 33, Folder 13)
      - King William Reservoir Project, 1998. (Box 33, Folder 14)
      - King William Reservoir Project, 1999. (Box 33, Folder 15)
      - King William Reservoir Project, 1999. (Box 33, Folder 16)
      - King William Reservoir Project, 1999-2000. (Box 34, Folder 1)
      - King William Reservoir Project, 2000-2001. (Box 34, Folder 2)
      - King William Reservoir Project, 2001. (Box 34, Folder 3)
      - King William Reservoir Project, 2001. (Box 34, Folder 4)
      - King William Reservoir Project, 2001. (Box 34, Folder 5)
      - King William Reservoir Project, 2001. (Box 34, Folder 6)
      - King William Reservoir Project, 2002. (Box 34, Folder 7)
      - King William Reservoir Project, 2002. (Box 34, Folder 8)
      - King William Reservoir Project, 2002. (Box 34, Folder 9)
      - King William Reservoir Project, 2002. (Box 34, Folder 10)
      - King William Reservoir Project, 2003. (Box 34, Folder 11)
      - King William Reservoir Project, 2003. (Box 34, Folder 12)
      - King William Reservoir Project, 2003. (Box 34, Folder 13)
      - King William Reservoir Project, 2003. (Box 34, Folder 14)
      - King William Reservoir Project, 2003. (Box 34, Folder 15)
      - King William Reservoir Project, 2003. (Box 34, Folder 16)
      - King William Reservoir Project, 2003. (Box 35, Folder 1)
      - King William Reservoir Project, 2004. (Box 35, Folder 2)
      - King William Reservoir Project, 2004. (Box 35, Folder 3)
      - King William Reservoir Project, 2004. (Box 35, Folder 4)
      - King William Reservoir Project, 2004. (Box 35, Folder 5)
      - King William Reservoir Project--Chesapeake Bay Foundation Comments, 2004. (Box 35, Folder 6)
      - King William Reservoir Project Petitions, 2003. (Box 35, Folder 7)
      - King William Reservoir Project Petitions, 2003. (Box 35, Folder 8)
      - King William Reservoir Project Petitions, 2003. (Box 35, Folder 9)
      - King William Reservoir Project Petitions, 2003. (Box 35, Folder 10)
      - King William Reservoir Project Petitions, 2003. (Box 35, Folder 11)
      - Newdunn Associates, 2002. (Box 35, Folder 12)
      - Newdunn Associates, 2002. (Box 35, Folder 13)
      - Non-Tidal Wetlands, 2002. (Box 35, Folder 14)
      - Non-Tidal Wetlands, 2002. (Box 35, Folder 15)
      - Nutrient Limits, 2003. (Box 36, Folder 1)
      - Nutrient Limits, 2003. (Box 36, Folder 2)
      - Nutrient Limits, 2003. (Box 36, Folder 3)
      - Nutrient Limits, 2003. (Box 36, Folder 4)
      - Nutrient Limits, 2003. (Box 36, Folder 5)
      - Nutrient Limits, 2003. (Box 36, Folder 6)
      - Nutrient Management, 2004. (Box 36, Folder 7)
      - Nutrient Management (JLARC Report), 2004. (Box 36, Folder 8)
      - Nutrient Management (JLARC Report), 2004. (Box 36, Folder 9)
      - Nutrient Tributary Strategy, 1999-2002. (Box 36, Folder 10)
      - Nutrient Tributary Strategy, 2003. (Box 36, Folder 11)
      - Nutrient Tributary Strategy, 2003. (Box 36, Folder 12)
      - Nutrient Tributary Strategy, 2003. (Box 36, Folder 13)
      - Nutrient Tributary Strategy, 2003. (Box 36, Folder 14)
      - Nutrient Tributary Strategy, 2003. (Box 36, Folder 15)
      - Nutrient Tributary Strategy, 2003. (Box 36, Folder 16)
      - Nutrient Tributary Strategy, 2004. (Box 36, Folder 17)
      - Nutrient Tributary Strategy, 2004. (Box 37, Folder 1)
      - Nutrient Tributary Strategy, 2004. (Box 37, Folder 2)
      - Nutrient Tributary Strategy, 2004. (Box 37, Folder 3)
      - Nutrient Tributary Strategy, 2004. (Box 37, Folder 4)
      - Nutrient Tributary Strategy, 2004. (Box 37, Folder 5)
      - Nutrient Tributary Strategy, 2004. (Box 37, Folder 6)
      - Nutrient Tributary Strategy, 2004. (Box 37, Folder 7)
      - Nutrient Tributary Strategy, 2004. (Box 37, Folder 8)
      - Nutrient Tributary Strategy, 2004. (Box 37, Folder 9)
      - Nutrient Tributary Strategy, 2004. (Box 37, Folder 10)
      - Nutrient Tributary Strategy, 2004. (Box 37, Folder 11)
      - Nutrient Tributary Strategy, 2004. (Box 37, Folder 12)
      - Nutrient Tributary Strategy, 2004. (Box 37, Folder 13)
      - Nutrient Tributary Strategy, 2004. (Box 37, Folder 14)
      - Nutrient Tributary Strategy, 2004. (Box 37, Folder 15)
      - Nutrient Tributary Strategy, 2004. (Box 37, Folder 16)
      - Nutrient Tributary Strategy, 2005. (Box 38, Folder 1)
      - Nutrient Tributary Strategy, 2005. (Box 38, Folder 2)
      - Nutrient Tributary Strategy, 2005. (Box 38, Folder 3)
      - Nutrient Tributary Strategy, 2005. (Box 38, Folder 4)
      - Nutrient Tributary Strategy, 2005. (Box 38, Folder 5)
      - Nutrient Tributary Strategy, 2005. (Box 38, Folder 6)
      - Nutrient Tributary Strategy, 2005. (Box 38, Folder 7)
      - Nutrient Tributary Strategy, 2005-2006. (Box 38, Folder 8)
      - Nutrient Tributary Strategy Comments, 2004. (Box 38, Folder 9)
      - Nutrient Tributary Strategy Comments, 2004. (Box 38, Folder 10)
      - Nutrient Tributary Strategy Comments, 2004. (Box 38, Folder 11)
      - Nutrient Tributary Strategy Comments, 2004. (Box 38, Folder 12)
      - Nutrient Tributary Strategy Comments, 2004. (Box 38, Folder 13)
      - Nutrient Tributary Strategy Comments, 2004. (Box 38, Folder 14)
      - Nutrient Tributary Strategy Comments, 2004. (Box 38, Folder 15)
      - Patriot Pipeline Project (Duke Energy), 2002. (Box 38, Folder 16)
      - Patriot Pipeline Project (Duke Energy), 2002. (Box 38, Folder 17)
      - Patriot Pipeline Project (Duke Energy), 2002. (Box 39, Folder 1)
      - Patriot Pipeline Project (Duke Energy), 2002-2003. (Box 39, Folder 2)
      - Patriot Pipeline Project (Duke Energy), 2003. (Box 39, Folder 3)
      - Patriot Pipeline Project (Duke Energy), 2003. (Box 39, Folder 4)
      - Power Plants (SCC Order), 2001. (Box 39, Folder 5)
      - Power Plants (SCC Order), 2001-2002. (Box 39, Folder 6)
      - Power Plants (SCC Order), 2002. (Box 39, Folder 7)
      - Power Plants (SCC Order), 2002. (Box 39, Folder 8)
      - Power Plants (SCC Order), 2002. (Box 39, Folder 9)
      - Power Plants (SCC Order), 2002. (Box 39, Folder 10)
      - Power Plants (SCC Order), 2002. (Box 39, Folder 11)
      - Power Plants (SCC Order), 2002. (Box 39, Folder 12)
      - Rappahannock River, 2002. (Box 39, Folder 13)
      - Regulations, 2002. (Box 39, Folder 14)
      - Roanoke Rapids / Gaston Dam Project, 2003. (Box 39, Folder 15)
      - Save Our Streams Program, 2002-2003. (Box 40, Folder 1)
      - Sewage Sludge, 2002. (Box 40, Folder 2)
      - Sewage Sludge, 2002. (Box 40, Folder 3)
      - Shenandoah River, 2002. (Box 40, Folder 4)
      - Smithfield Foods, 2001-2003. (Box 40, Folder 5)
      - Southeast Rural Community Assistance Project, 2002-2003. (Box 40, Folder 6)
      - Total Maximum Daily Load (TMDL), 2000-2001. (Box 40, Folder 7)
      - Total Maximum Daily Load (TMDL), 2002-2003. (Box 40, Folder 8)
      - Tributyltin (TBT), 1996-2002. (Box 40, Folder 9)
      - Tri-Cities Properties (Garcia Project), 2002. (Box 40, Folder 10)
      - Tri-Cities Properties (Garcia Project), 2003. (Box 40, Folder 11)
      - Tri-Cities Properties (Garcia Project), 2003. (Box 40, Folder 12)
      - Tri-Cities Properties (Garcia Project), 2003. (Box 40, Folder 13)
      - Tri-Cities Properties (Garcia Project), 2003. (Box 40, Folder 14)
      - Tri-Cities Properties (Garcia Project), 2003. (Box 40, Folder 15)
      - Tri-Cities Properties (Garcia Project), 2003. (Box 40, Folder 16)
      - Tri-Cities Properties (Garcia Project), 2003. (Box 40, Folder 17)
      - Tri-Cities Properties (Garcia Project), 2003. (Box 41, Folder 1)
      - Tri-Cities Properties (Garcia Project), 2003. (Box 41, Folder 2)
      - Tri-Cities Properties (Garcia Project), 2003. (Box 41, Folder 3)
      - Tri-Cities Properties (Garcia Project), 2003. (Box 41, Folder 4)
      - Tri-Cities Properties (Garcia Project), 2003. (Box 41, Folder 5)
      - Tri-Cities Properties (Garcia Project), 2003. (Box 41, Folder 6)
      - U.S.S. Cole Memorial Reef, 2002-2003. (Box 41, Folder 7)
      - Virginia v. Maryland, 2002. (Box 41, Folder 8)
      - Virginia v. Maryland, 2002. (Box 41, Folder 9)
      - Virginia v. Maryland, 2002. (Box 41, Folder 10)
      - Virginia v. Maryland, 2002. (Box 41, Folder 11)
      - Virginia v. Maryland, 2002. (Box 41, Folder 12)
      - Virginia v. Maryland, 2002. (Box 41, Folder 13)
      - Virginia v. Maryland, 2002. (Box 41, Folder 14)
      - Virginia v. Maryland, 2002. (Box 42, Folder 1)
      - Virginia v. Maryland, 2002. (Box 42, Folder 2)
      - Virginia v. Maryland, 2002. (Box 42, Folder 3)
      - Virginia v. Maryland, 2002. (Box 42, Folder 4)
      - Virginia v. Maryland, 2002. (Box 42, Folder 5)
      - Virginia v. Maryland, 2002. (Box 42, Folder 6)
      - Virginia Tech Water Resources Research Center, 2002-2003. (Box 42, Folder 7)
      - Virginia Water Policy, 1998-2002. (Box 42, Folder 8)
      - Virginia Water Policy, 2002. (Box 42, Folder 9)
      - Virginia Water Policy, 2002. (Box 42, Folder 10)
      - Virginia Water Policy, 2002-2003. (Box 42, Folder 11)
      - Wastewater Treatment, 2002-2003. (Box 42, Folder 12)
      - Water Issues (misc.), 2001-2002. (Box 42, Folder 13)
      - Water Issues (misc.), 2002. (Box 42, Folder 14)
      - Water Issues (misc.), 2003-2005. (Box 43, Folder 1)
      - Water Program Consolidation, 2002. (Box 43, Folder 2)
      - Water Quality, 2002. (Box 43, Folder 3)
      - Water Quality, 2003-2005. (Box 43, Folder 4)
      - Water Quality Improvement Fund, 2005. (Box 43, Folder 5)
      - Watershed Planning / Permitting, 2001-2005. (Box 43, Folder 6)
      - Watershed Planning / Permitting, 2005. (Box 43, Folder 7)
      - Wetlands, 2003. (Box 43, Folder 8)
      - Wetlands, 2003-2004. (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Administrative, 2002. (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Administrative, 2003. (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - Administrative, 2003-2006. (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - Coastal Resource Management Program, 2002-2003. (Box 43, Folder 13)
    - Comprehensive Environmental Data System (CEDS) Oversight, 1999-2001. (Box 43, Folder 14)
    - Environmental Education, 2000-2002. (Box 43, Folder 15)
    - Environmental Education, 2002-2003. (Box 43, Folder 16)
    - Environmental Education, 2003-2004. (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - Environmental Protection Agency--General Correspondence, 2002-2003. (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - Environmental Protection Agency--General Correspondence, 2003. (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - Environmental Protection Agency--General Correspondence, 2004-2005. (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Environmental Protection Agency--Metro Washington Air Quality Committee, 2004-2005. (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Environmental Protection Agency--Metro Washington Air Quality Committee, 2004-2005. (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - Environmental Council of the States--Annual Meeting, 2005. (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Environmental Council of the States--EPA 2007 Planning Meeting, 2005. (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - Environmental Council of the States--State Secretaries Meeting (Sec. Murphy), 2005. (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - Environmental Council of the States--State Secretaries Meeting (Sec. Murphy), 2005. (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - Environmental Council of the States--State Secretaries Meeting (David Paylor), 2005. (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - Executive Agreement, 2003-2004. (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - General Correspondence, 2001-2002. (Box 44, Folder 13)
    - General Correspondence, 2002. (Box 44, Folder 14)
    - General Correspondence, 2003. (Box 44, Folder 15)
    - General Correspondence, 2003. (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - General Correspondence, 2003. (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - General Correspondence, 2003. (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - General Correspondence, 2004. (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - General Correspondence, 2004. (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - General Correspondence, 2004. (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - General Correspondence, 2004. (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - General Correspondence, 2004. (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - General Correspondence, 2004. (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - General Correspondence, 2004. (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - General Correspondence, 2005. (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - General Correspondence, 2005. (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - General Correspondence, 2005. (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - Health Department / DEQ Memo of Understanding, 1998. (Box 45, Folder 14)
    - Innovative Technology, 2002. (Box 45, Folder 15)
    - Innovative Technology, 2003. (Box 45, Folder 16)
    - Organisation for Economic Co-Operation and Development (OECD), 2005. (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Organisation for Economic Co-Operation and Development (OECD), 2005. (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Oyster Heritage Program, 1999-2003. (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Small Business Innovation Research and Development, 2001. (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Virginia Environmental Emergency Response Fund, 2000. (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Virginia Environmental Stewardship Awards, 2002. (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Virginia Environmental Stewardship Awards, 2003. (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - Virginia Environmental Stewardship Awards, 2003. (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - Virginia Environmental Stewardship Awards, 2003. (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - Virginia Environmental Stewardship Awards, 2003. (Box 46, Folder 10)
    - Virginia Environmental Stewardship Awards, 2003. (Box 46, Folder 11)
    - Virginia Environmental Stewardship Awards, 2003. (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Virginia Environmental Stewardship Awards, 2003. (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Virginia Environmental Stewardship Awards, 2003. (Box 46, Folder 14)
    - Virginia Environmental Stewardship Awards, 2004. (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Virginia Environmental Stewardship Awards, 2004. (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Virginia Environmental Stewardship Awards, 2004. (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Virginia Environmental Stewardship Awards, 2004. (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Virginia Environmental Stewardship Awards, 2004. (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Virginia Environmental Stewardship Awards, 2005. (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Virginia Environmental Stewardship Awards, 2005. (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Virginia Environmental Stewardship Awards, 2005. (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - Virginia Environmental Stewardship Awards, 2005. (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - Virginia Resources Authority, 2003. (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - Wind Energy, 2003-2005. (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Game and Inland Fisheries, Department of, 1995-2006. (Box 48-51.)
    The Virginia Department of Game and Inland Fisheries (DGIF) is responsible for the management of inland fisheries, wildlife, and recreational boating for the Commonwealth of Virginia. DGIF seeks to provide opportunities for all to enjoy wildlife, inland fish, boating and related outdoor recreation. The agency also works to promote safety for persons and property in connection with boating, hunting and fishing.
    This subseries contains general correspondence and administrative information, as well as files devoted to particular projects and issues such as elk hunting and chronic wasting disease, the "roadless rule," and various aspects of wildlife management.
    - Administrative, 2000-2001. (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - Administrative, 2002. (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Administrative, 2002-2003. (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Administrative, 2003-2004. (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Administrative, 2004-2005. (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Administrative, 2005-2006. (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Big Survey, 2002. (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - Boating, 2002-2005. (Box 48, Folder 8)
    - Elk in Virginia, 2001-2002. (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - Elk in Virginia, 2002. (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - Elk in Virginia, 2002. (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - Executive Agreement, 2002. (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - Fish Passage, 2002. (Box 48, Folder 13)
    - FLW Outdoors, 2002-2004. (Box 48, Folder 14)
    - General Correspondence, 2002. (Box 48, Folder 15)
    - General Correspondence, 2002. (Box 48, Folder 16)
    - General Correspondence, 2003. (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - General Correspondence, 2003. (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - General Correspondence, 2003. (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - General Correspondence, 2003. (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - General Correspondence, 2003. (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - General Correspondence, 2004. (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - General Correspondence, 2004. (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - General Correspondence, 2004. (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - General Correspondence, 2004. (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - General Correspondence, 2005. (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - General Correspondence, 2005. (Box 49, Folder 11)
    - General Correspondence, 2005. (Box 49, Folder 12)
    - General Correspondence, 2005-2006. (Box 49, Folder 13)
    - Goshen / Little North Mountain Wildlife Area, 2002. (Box 49, Folder 14)
    - Goshen / Little North Mountain Wildlife Area, 2002. (Box 49, Folder 15)
    - Hunting, 2002. (Box 49, Folder 16)
    - Hunting, 2003-2005. (Box 50, Folder 1)
    - Hunters for the Hungry, 2002. (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Orion Estate Shooting Preserve, 2005. (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Orion Estate Shooting Preserve, 2005. (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - Proposed Smith Mountain Lake Regional Office, 1995-2005. (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Proposed Smith Mountain Lake Regional Office, 1995-2005. (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Randol, Dr. Arthur G., 2002. (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - Roadless Rule, 2003-2004. (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - Roadless Rule, 2005. (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - Roadless Rule, 2005. (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - Roadless Rule, 2005. (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - Roadless Rule, 2005. (Box 50, Folder 12)
    - Shad Management, 2002. (Box 50, Folder 13)
    - Virginia Comprehensive Wildlife Conservation Strategy, 2005. (Box 50, Folder 14)
    - Virginia Comprehensive Wildlife Conservation Strategy, 2005. (Box 50, Folder 15)
    - Waterfowl Hunting and Blind Laws, 2002-2003. (Box 50, Folder 16)
    - Wetlands Restoration Coordinating Committee, 2001. (Box 50, Folder 17)
    - Wildlife, 2002. (Box 50, Folder 18)
    - Wildlife, 2003-2005. (Box 51, Folder 1)
    - Zebra Mussel, 2003-2005. (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Historic Resources, Department of, 2000-2006. (Box 51-54.)
    The Virginia Department of Historic Resources (DHR) serves as the State Historic Preservation Office. The agency's mission is to foster and support the stewardship of Virginia's significant historic, architectural, archaeological, and cultural resources.
    This subseries contains general correspondence, much of which is devoted to pleas to save historic properties, as well as administrative information about the agency. Other files pertain to projects and issues such as those involving the Shenandoah Battlefields Foundation, the Clarkton Bridge over the Staunton River in southside Virginia, preservation of buildings at the Medical College of Virginia campus in Richmond, and most notably, the opening of the Tredegar National Civil War Center, also in Richmond.
    - Administrative, 2001-2002. (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Administrative, 2002-2003. (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Administrative, 2003-2006. (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - APVA Preservation Virginia, 2004. (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - APVA Preservation Virginia, 2004. (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Bed Tower / Museum of the Confederacy, 2004. (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Clarkton Bridge, 2003. (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - Clarkton Bridge, 2003. (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - Clarkton Bridge, 2004. (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - Executive Agreement, 2002-2005. (Box 51, Folder 12)
    - General Correspondence, 2002. (Box 51, Folder 13)
    - General Correspondence, 2002. (Box 51, Folder 14)
    - General Correspondence, 2003. (Box 51, Folder 15)
    - General Correspondence, 2003. (Box 51, Folder 16)
    - General Correspondence, 2003. (Box 51, Folder 17)
    - General Correspondence, 2003. (Box 52, Folder 1)
    - General Correspondence, 2004. (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - General Correspondence, 2004. (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - General Correspondence, 2004. (Box 52, Folder 4)